It's my life, it's your life!
Fightin' for tomorrow, go
catch what you really want!
I want more, anyone more?
Come on, walkin' up the door!
It's my life, it's your life!
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah!
I know you're strong!
Believe you can achieve your call!
Let's keep on going, I'll not stay.
Let's do it again.
You know what I mean, baby!
No one can make my dream come true!
Don't you feel it?
I really don't know what is
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away the great
end of the unknown.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you.
It's my life, it's your life.
But if you don't want to
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can't achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your eyes that
I want, but you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life,
shine like a star to be good.
I know you're strong, just that
you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going out of day.
You make my day every day.
Have you ever shattered your blade before?
Yeah.
It's happened a couple of times.
Cracked a few of them fighting you.
Infused with Haki.
Those swords would have been
able to withstand the stress.
You must carry every
nick as a mark of shame.
Any sword can become a black blade!
A black blade?
Until you master this, no liquor Huh?
No nicks on the edge.
Are there any casualties reported?
No, sir.
All thanks to your help.
Your quick thinking saved
a lot of lives today.
Suspending gravity on the
falling debris was brilliant.
Luckily, we had time to react since we
had a lot of the evacuees gathered here.
I'm relieved to hear that.
Did you see?
The giant statue was split into two.
Does that mean one of the
executives was defeated?
Lord Dinko was taken out!
I can't believe someone with power
like that didn't enter the tournament.
Must be a humble guy.
And he's a mere subordinate
to Garp's grandson.
Ha, ha, ha.
Gotta hand it to him.
King Rick has been saved, so I
suppose I'll let him slide this once.
Mr. Zoro!
Oh, that's the factory.
Something caused it to burst into flames.
How'd that happen?
We ready for one more?
Let's go!
All right!
Put it to the ground!
It made us suffer!
That'll be the last times of
jerk tricks us into slavery!
Hey, hey!
Looks like Pika was taken down and now
the factory's been set on fire, Kofi!
But what they don't
quite realize yet is our
defeated can revive and our
factory can be repaired.
That's because we still have Mon Cherie on
our side with the heal-heal fruit power!
Rebecca!
Taka!
Robin Wind!
Are you okay?
Wait, is that really you, Commander Keros?
Yes, you've rescued the princess, I see.
You look so valiant, even
more than the statue!
You flatter me.
My goodness, you've been terribly injured.
Please allow me to heal you at once.
One moment.
So you're Princess Muncheri.
I've heard word of your
remarkable ability,
but there must be a limit on
its use, not wasted on me.
But you're wounded.
Just let me help you.
I'll be fine.
I'm conscious, aren't I?
More importantly, you're safe.
It must have been hard on you.
If you're set on using your power to help,
There are going to be countless
citizens who need you more than I
This is really our home
Leo mentioned that the situation was dire,
but I didn't expect something
like this At least we
successfully destroyed the
factory The final clash is upon us
The kingdom has long suffered under
Doflamingo's clutches It shall either
be liberated and returned to King
Rick Or once again fall into despair
Her last line of hope lies
among a pirate crew now.
Is that so?
Our fate shall be decided.
At the royal palace.
Save us, Lawland.
Lufieland This is it.
It's all on them.
Lufy
Try thing.
Go, Lufy.
Okay, I infiltrated the Rampart Tower.
Things are looking dicey in here, though.
Can you make it to me, Sabo?
I'm helping some of the trapped
prisoners escape the Coliseum grounds.
Sorry, but you're way too far from me.
I know for a fact you've handled much
tougher missions than this, Koala.
I wouldn't call if this was a cakewalk.
Luffy might be at risk to be right there.
Hey, sorrow?
Do you need a hand?
I'm fine.
Not even a scratch.
I was scared!
I thought you might die!
Actually, I was more afraid
that I might die, so thank you!
Sir Zoro, splendid work back there!
Yeah, thank you, Mr.
Pirate.
I can't believe you cut down that
massive statue with just swords.
That was crazy!
Hold the applause, guys!
We're not in the clear just yet.
Once that cage is gone,
then you can cheer.
As long as that stands, the main
thorn in our side is still out there.
Oh, my God.
Stop!
That's enough, Bellamy!
Cut the crap!
Stop it!
That jerk isn't worth
trading your life for!
I made my choice!
Stop with that crap!
Hey, you're in rough shape, Bellamy.
If you keep fighting me like this.
You really are gonna die!
Even if I die.
I can take you down with me.
If nothing else?
Maybe Doflamingo will think
on me fondly when I'm gone.
He said you're free!
Take it and walk!
Fine, Bellamy.
I've had my fun.
You're free from me now.
just like you've always been right
you can just go why risk your
life listen to me Bellamy he knew
you'd do this and he doesn't care
that may be true but so what I ain't
gonna turn my back on him even if I
If that's what it takes to get him
to respect me, then I'm gonna do it!
You big liar!
This isn't about loyalty!
It's about your pride!
If you have it all figured out,
then shut up and fight me already!
You'll die for nothing!
This is the end of the road for me.
No, this is what I want.
To be killed.
By the only other man I ever respected.
Where are you going?
Up there.
Bellamy did change.
You take that back now!
You now have changed, Bellamy.
You're my friend!
Thank you, Straw Hats.
Straw Hats!
Fine!
If you won't take me seriously,
then I have no other choice!
Don't think I won't kill you!
Stop being such a coward!
Put your soaps up already!
This is it!
One final blow and it's all over!
Go to hell!
One last chance to do this, Straw Hat!
Thank you.
Thank you for calling me a friend.
I know I'm pitiful, I know
I looked up to the wrong.
I don't need to hear it from you!
I have to hold on to something!
Even a loser like me has some dignity!
To Flamengo!
I can hear the howling of a wild cur.
Why don't you limp on up here?
Hello.
Your buddy's on his way.
This is going to be good.
I'm sure he'll be surprised to see you.
Or rather, your corpse.
Take it easy, Law. Rest.
Clearly, you've lost this.
Fight both of us?
What were you thinking?
Come on.
I'm more than enough for you.
And Straw Hat.
He's a bit busy.
Still,
shame he doesn't have the guts to put that
so-called friend of his out of his misery.
Otherwise, he might have saved you.
What a poor naïve toad.
Born into the hell known as White Town.
A bleak future awaited you since boyhood.
Then, in a twist of fate, you were
led to my younger brother, Corazon.
Which managed to draw your life out a
bit longer But now you're nothing more
than his vindictive ghost a revenge
driven fool kept alive by hatred alone
You've really made the
most out of the rotten hand
fate dealt you still your
tenacity won't save you now
Thirteen years down the drain.
I do pity you in a way a
wasted life
within moments you'll be
food for the worms you
worked hard but for what well
it doesn't have to be for
nothing trafalgar d water
law come on don't let that
power go to waste this is
your final shot so listen
you've been given a chance
to change this world so do
the perpetual youth surgery
put that abob fruit to good
use then you die and since
I'm a fair man in exchange
I'll grant you whatever you
desire I mean that would
be a tough deal for me to pass all
right i'm in you're smarter than i
thought la helping us out goofy's
gonna be eternally grateful whatever
my wish is for you to bring back
cora and when you're done i want you
to lick the asses of every last person
in this kingdom you think i'm no
match for you?
It's all in the bag?
We're a joke.
Here's the truth, Doflamingo.
When you lose,
don't act shocked.
The Straw Hat Pirates have performed
countless miracles along their journeys.
Someone like you never had
a chance of stopping them.
Also, you're wrong if you
think you can Get Caesar back.
Show respect—that,
stuffy you're talking to!
What
you don't realize is that it's
your head on the chopping?
chopping
Oh, your jacket, it says
Corazon, are you mocking me?
And the heart pirates,
you think I didn't notice?
What are you trying to say here?
You refuse to accept the heart seat.
Then you bear the mark
of the heart anyway.
Why?
How insufferable.
Law, Corazon, that's enough.
This ends here.
Your crusade is dead and gone.
I'm finally free of this burden.
I'm free!
He can't proceed.
He has taken down Bellamy.
Well done.
Now there are only two
higher-ups left remaining.
Keep strong, Straw Hat.
He's making great strides. However,
the final obstacles awaiting him are
trouble, and, of course, Doflamingo himself.
No!
Viola!
Something wrong?
Viola?
I have terrible news.
We're down a man too.
What's that mean?
Is someone in trouble?
It's Trafalgar Law.
King Rick?
Despite our victories, the kingdom
is in great danger. Let's go.
Citizens may still require our aid.
We can't rest yet.
Sir, I'm coming.
Uh, me too! I'm joining
you. Count me in. Me too!
Very well.
Let us descend into town.
It is not too late to minimize
the casualties further true.
Even if we can't fight
we can still help out
So what's the next step.
Let's wrap this up, sound good? Trouble!
TOPLAMENKO!
Took you long enough, Straw Hat.
How's dear old Bellamy doing?
Now that he has his freedom...
Don't play dumb!
You set this all up!
You knew he'd never run away.
Come, come.
Spiderweb spread out.
Interesting.
So I guess Bellamy didn't
hightail it after all?
What's so funny?
Now come, come!
Hulk got my gun!
And now, break white!
Hey, Traffy!
Where's all this blood coming from?
Where'd your arm go?
Hey, Traffy! Hang in there!
Hey, Traffy!
What you can't tell—he's dead. Liar!
Just look at him.
Trafi was holding out
for you to come through.
What a damn shame!
He
did mention that you're quite
the miracle worker, Straw Hat.
I
don't know.
You didn't impress me
much in our first fight.
fight
And I doubt you stand a
chance against both of us.
You'll pay for this, you bastards!
Wait!
Hold your positions!
Oh, no!
Let's back up!
That's shrinking!
You'll be joining your
pal, Law, in no time.
And now...
We end this game. Mingo!
Wait.
Listen carefully, Straw Hat.
Oh no!
It's moving! I knew it!
Those killer strings!
They're closing ends!
Run away!
The end of the town isn't safer anymore!
Go, go, go!
Say thank you in the west!
Reporting from Carta in the east.
The birdcage is moving,
as the report said.
Everyone is fleeing to
downtown in a panic!
No one will survive.
They'll all be butchered sooner or later.
Oh, I'm sorry.
The rules have changed.
I've decided to play a different game now.
You're still calling this a game?
Just listen.
The birdcage that surrounds
the kingdom started shrinking,
pulling into the center bit by bit.
Think of it like a giant
umbrella closing slowly.
It'll cut through everything in
its path, the entire kingdom.
As for how long that'll take,
well, about an hour, I'd say.
They have nowhere left
to go; they're finished.
Check for citizens at the edge of the
kingdom and bring them to the center quickly,
yes sir!
We've moved the people at risk
from the edges of the kingdom,
but we have to keep going.
Let's go!
Follow after me!
The strings are coming!
Hurry!
Hey, could somebody untie us, please?
Just the feet is fine, okay?
Have mercy!
I don't want to die!
What?
The birdcage is freaking? No!
Hey, birdcage, stop it!
It seems to be so.
Come on, really?
What should we do?
We've suffered enough already!
Zoro, help!
And we were winning
all of our fights, too!
You can't pull the rug
out from under us now!
Huh?
We finally made it out of that
dungeon after all this time?
And now we're in a new cage?
There has to be some
place safe we can run to!
How could you do such a heartless thing?
Is there no depth you
won't sink to, Doflamingo?
The birdcage is going to dice up
the whole kingdom at this rate!
We're all done for!
Our home, too!
I'm seeing a lot of smoke and
hearing a lot of rumbling.
There's no way this is good.
Hurry it up, Luffy!
Just kick his ass and
get this mess over with!
You're our only hope! Indeed!
Thwart him swiftly, my friend!
It must be difficult to have so
much resting on one man's shoulders.
Sir Luffy!
Please prevail!
Everyone will die if you do not succeed!
I won't spare a single
rotten life in this kingdom.
They aren't worth a thing to me.
Not since they discovered the truth
about how I've been running this place.
Every building, every
person, every animal,
all your miserable little allies,
and finally you will die.
Although I suppose some of
your friends have died already,
the good doctor passed away.
just a moment ago.
So much for your pirate
alliance with dear old Traffy.
Oh, but no need to worry about me.
I'll build a new kingdom.
Yeah, screw that.
All I gotta do is kick your ass
and everything will be fine.
I'm starting to think that you're not
paying attention to me, Straw Hat?
You'll never learn, do you?
Bullet strip
I'm gone Go ahead.
You'll die just like Loh.
Shambles.
Sorry, but nobody's dying here except you.
Go!
This operation will destroy
your body from the inside out.
Give a knife!
You were supposed to be
dead, you big cheater!
And how can you do an app-a-tag
without making a room? I did.
We're in a room as we speak.
It'll shave some time
off my life, I'm sure.
But I made a room so big that you
can't see the end of it from here.
What?
But that's crazy!
All I did was in
preparation for this moment!
It wasn't enough to kill me.
Shambles!
Mingo!
Wait.
I'm alive.
Listen carefully, Straw Hat.
Don't turn around.
I have a plan.
You can't defend against an attack.
I'm inside!
Even you can counteract this technique.
Doofy!
You're a king!
A king never fought to his knees!
You little bastard.
It's no use.
Even if you kill me, you're done for.
You think I won't kill you anyway?
You forget about me?
I've got a gun, Chester!
Oh, no!
Dolphi!
Are you okay?
What more? Straw Hat. Hold on.
Traffy It has to be.
Me who does this!
It's over, Doflamingo.
What have you done?
You're me!
How dare you!
Don't get in our way!
Your family...
is nothing more than people
you thought you could use.
A bond built entirely on
your own ego and convenience.
And your only true brother.
Who tried to stop you on
your path to destruction?
Was murdered by you.
Cause Lost finally, free now!
Yeah, I know.
That was unfortunate.
But he was the one who betrayed me.
He was the one who pointed a gun.
You think I wanted that?
Don't give me that crap!
You knew damn well he
wouldn't pull that trigger.
I could have pulled it just fine.
I bet so.
I always knew we were the same.
I want to destroy everything that I see.
People, towns.
I want to burn this whole
world to the ground.
Maybe so.
But in this case, that's fine.
Cause, I'll tell you this.
You were the one who
should have died that day.
If you're expecting me to say
something cold and twisted?
Then I'll indulge you.
I hated Corazon.
He was a nuisance and an obstacle to me.
His insipid sense of justice.
This is worthless
sentimentality holding me back.
He wasn't worth a damn.
And that's why, when I killed
him that day, I was happy.
Go to shock!
You go to hell!
I've heard enough!
Help me!
Oh, my God.
That's our cake for ya!
Can't keep a straight man down!
What did you do?
if i have enough time i can use my
powers to perform an operation of my own
right now beneath the skin my strings are
reconstructing the organs
you so rudely damaged
what the hell just takes
creativity although
i don't know if i would
call this It's healing,
exactly.
You threw your life away.
Sticky, sticky cheese!
Let me go!
Stick sticker!
And look at that.
I still get to do the honors.
Damn it!
Damn it.
Thank you.